BALASUBRAMANIAN.S

12-01-38, Pattuppannai street,

Poolankudiyiruppu. sengottai,

Tenkasi Dist-627813

Telephone: 09047529743

Email: mail4bala93@gmail.com

PERSONAL PROFILE

Over 09 years of experience, electrical supervisor scope of Electrical (transformer, all electrical equipment installation, testing, commissioning and maintenance) and electrical system projects that include new building and renovation works. Proven track record of Success in achieving Time, Budget and quality goals on a broad

**PROJECT MANAGEMENT:** 

Process in depth knowledge of system practices and regulatory compliance issues. Qualified to review and evaluate Bid documents, estimate cost, chart projections, write and negotiate contracts and lead cross functional project teams. Coordinate activities effectively with responsible parties regarding guidelines and scope.

**RELATIONSHIP DEVELOPMENT:** 

Excellent leadership, communication and relationship building skills, work effectively with engineers, architects, client representatives, building officials, contractors, building managers, inspectors and other industry professionals. Work jointly with clients to review job progress and address outstanding issues: provided the highest level of service to clients, earning frequent commendations as a result

#### Technical SKILLS

- Electrical Wiring & Cable works
- Panel erection works
- Lighting arrestor installation
- Network & Communication Systems
- Maintenance of all electrical works
- maintenance and handling electrical equipment

# Experience

### **Electrical supervisor**

### M/s Consolidated Construction Consortium Ltd.

may 2013 – may 2015

## M/s Blueeyee Multiitech Pvt Ltd.

June 2015- May 2022 date.

#### Work duties:

- Develops strategic electrical plans by studying operational plans
- Determining needs to accomplish operational plans
- Updating and modifying requirements and solutions
- Planning, monitoring, appraising, and reviewing job contributions.
- Preparing and completing action plans / reports
- Establishing installation schedules
- Plans electrical projects by determining specifications
- o Integrating requirements with architectural and mechanical designs
- Maintains electrical systems by establishing and enforcing preventive and on-going maintenance
- Scheduling repairs; coordinating shut-downs and installations

# ACADEMIC QUALIFICATIONS

Arulmigu Senthil Andavar Polytechnic College 2010-2013 (Electrical & Electronic Engineering)

SMSS Govt Boys Higher Secondary School2006-2010 (9 to +2)

# Declaration

The Above Mentioned details are True to the best of my Knowledge

Date: Yours Truthfully

Place: (Balasubramanian.S)